字幕翻译/压制：旋火
视频来源：youtu.be/0rLcsVpqTIY
原视频发布日期：20200419
原作者名：NASASpaceflight
大家好 这里是NASASpaceflight的Julia
Hi everyone this is Julia from NASASpaceflight.
今天我在这里卡纳维拉尔港 跟你说说港口最近都有啥新鲜事儿
I'm here in Port Canaveral today to give you a little bit of an update of what's going on in port
还有SpaceX船队的事情
and what's going on with the SpaceX fleet.
我们离发射大概只剩几天时间
We are just a few days away from launch.
截止2020年4月20日 发射日期提前至4月22日(当地时间)
第7个星链任务目前定于4月23日也就是这周四
The seventh StarLink mission is scheduled for April 23rd which would be this Thursday.
这意味着什么？
What does that mean?
这意味着我身后的船里至少有一艘是要马上离开的
Well that means at least one of the ships behind me is going to be leaving soon.
中间的那个是GO寻求号
GO Quest, the one in the center.
她是船队里最长的
She has been with the fleet the longest
也是搭乘人员的船只
that is the crew support ship
她们通常在我当然仍爱你号离开后几小时内离开
And they usually leave a few hours after Of Course I Still Love You leaves.
关于这一点 OCISLY号会被另一艘船拖走
On that note Of Course I Still Love You will be being towed by a guest tug.
鹰号是一个拖船 forum.nasaspaceflight.com/index.php?topic=39766.2280
鹰号正在南下 进行一些补给的工作
Hawk is currently down south doing some tender work.
Finn Falgout号也是一艘拖船
那么 我们会看到Finn Falgout号 来拖拽OCISLY号
So we're going to see Finn Falgout take out Of Course I Still Love You
到时我们会核查一下
and we'll check that out in a little bit.
我只需要在这里快速讲解两件事情
I'm just gonna a quick show off a couple things here.
我身后就是GO搜寻者号
Right behind me that is GO Searcher.
GO 搜寻者号是载人龙飞船的主要回收船
GO Searcher is the main crew dragon recovery vessel.
在宇航员从国际空间站返回地球也就是DM2任务时 我们会看到他们的行动
We'll see them in action for DM2 when our astronauts return to Earth from the space station.
之前已经说过了GO寻求号
We talked about GO Quest already.
她们是在外出回收时主要的搭乘人员的船只
They are the primary crew vessel when they go out for recovery
也就是她们带来了船员和物资
which means they bring out crew and supplies.
一旦一级火箭着陆以后 他们就会上OCISLY号去固定它
They'll board Of Course I Still Love You to secure the booster once it has landed
或者在其他情况下 他们需要回收没有落在甲板上的一级火箭
or in some other cases they may have to babysit a booster if it didn't quite make it on deck.
接着就是第三艘船GO领航员号
And then we have our third ship over here that is GO Navigator.
她的布置和GO搜寻者号差不多
She is decked out much like GO Searcher is.
而且她也参与龙飞船回收演练
And she does practice our capsule recovery.
她是GO搜寻者号的备份 也会参与任务
She is secondary to GO Searcher and does also go out on mission.
那么现在已经看过了这三艘船
So now we've seen these three.
让我们停顿了一会儿 我要带你们去那儿
Let's pause for a moment and I'm going to take you over there
去看看OCISLY号
and see Of Course I Still Love You
还有发生在只要读下说明书号的有趣的事情
and all of the fun things going on with Just Read the Instructions.
那么在我去看OCISLY号的路上
Well on my way over to see Of Course I Still Love You,
我发现 有些飞船可以给你们看下
I noticed that we have a couple capsules of interest to show you.
这些是用于测试的飞船
These are test capsules.
最靠近我们的那个实际上在GO搜寻者号上面
The closest one is actually on GO Searcher.
它是一个更精确的载人龙飞船的模型
And it's a higher fidelity model of the crew dragon.
更远点的地方 是另一个在GO领航员号上面的载人龙飞船模型
And then you've got the one a little bit further back on GO Navigator.
那个就粗糙一些
And that's a little bit less detail.
因此看来 它可能是昨天离开的港口
So it appears that it is possible when they went out of port yesterday
他们使用吊机来演练飞船的回收
they were using the hoist and practicing recovering that capsule
并把它放回网里
and putting it back on the nest.
让我们回到OCISLY号
Let's go back over to Of Course I Still Love You.
我们是在北部6号货运码头
We are at North cargo pier 6 right now.
通常在这里你会看到OCISLY号停泊下来
This is normally where you would see Of Course I Still Love You berth
当他们带着一级火箭返回的时候
when they return with a booster.
实际上 你会看到那个一旦把火箭从OCISLY号放下来的时候 放置火箭的支架
In fact you can see the stand that they would place the booster on once they take it off Of Course I Still Love You.
就在只要读下说明书号的右边
It is just to the right of Just Read the Instructions.
那么当然我们想说下只要读下说明书号
So of course we want to talk about Just Read the Instructions.
你能看到船头船尾布满了各种各样的货物集装箱
You can see look at all of those cargo containers on the bow and stern.
值得注意的是实际上有两个安装好的发动发动机吊舱
Of note there are actually two of the new thruster pods installed already.
因此 新的发动机放在水里
So the new thrusters are in the water.
同时你会看到剩下的两个需要安装的发动机还放在甲板上
And you can see the remaining two that need to be installed on deck.
如果我们仔细地看实际上还能看到有些人在甲板上工作
If we look really really close you can actually see some people working on deck today.
那么 这些东西的尺寸就可以拿人来对比
So there's your people for scale.
人相比于集装箱还有发动机而言真的太小了
They are crazy tiny compared to the size of these containers and these thrusters.
我迫不及待地想看看这艘船能做些什么
I cannot wait to see what this can do.
我的理解是
My understanding is
每个这样的发动机都等同于鹰号或者类似的运作中的拖船的发动机大小
each of those thrusters is the equivalent of what Hawk or a tug of that size would have to operate with
这有可能说明只要读下说明书号可能是完全自动的
which gives us the possibility that maybe Just Read the Instructions could be fully autonomous
而无需拖船协助去回收区
and not need a tug assist to get to the recovery zone.
这显然是仍有待观察
That obviously is yet to be seen.
我们要看看他们在获得资格方面有什么障碍
We'll have to see what kind of obstacles they have for licensing.
在最初的几次运行中可能他们还是想要用拖船来完成作业
And they'll probably want to take a tug out for those first few runs when she's operational.
只是为了确保一切是安全的 而它能按预期工作
Just to ensure that everything is safe and it's working as expected.
当我们往北稍微看一点儿的时候
As we look a little bit more to the north though,
会看到这两个姐妹船
you see our two sister ships.
GO Chief女士在右边
We've got GO Ms. Chief on the right.
我更喜欢叫她Chief女士
I like to call her just Ms. Chief
和GO Tree女士或者说Tree女士在左侧
and GO Ms. Tree or Ms. Tree on the left.
这两艘船负责回收整流罩
These two faring catchers are the ones who have been working to bring those fairings back.
那么 差不多是
So we should have it sounds like
周四的第7次星链任务发射会使用回收过的整流罩
we do have recovered fairings on the seventh StarLink mission launching on thursday.
所以 希望它们能再回收成功一次
So hopefully they can be re-recovering.
我们可以看看它们在另一场任务中的表现
We can see how well they do on another mission.
我来放大一点点看看
I'm going to zoom in a little bit and see.
看起来甲板上没有任何人 也不像是正在准备的样子
It doesn't appear that anyone is on deck right now getting ready.
那么 以后我们会查看OCISLY号 接下来的情况
So we're gonna have to check and see what's going on with Of Course I Still Love You.
拍摄日期为2020年4月18日周六
我估计 她们大概也就是明天晚上或者周一早上 在任务之前离开这里
I expect that they will be leaving on if not tomorrow night then Monday morning ahead of mission.
需要3天半左右的时间去回收区域
It does take a good three and a half or so days to get to the recovery zone
就在卡纳维拉尔港的东北方(的海域)
and that'll be to the northeast of Port Canaveral.
我还需要再动一动
I'm going to move one more time.
试试能不能看到 OCISLY号
Let's see if we can get a look of Of Course I Still Love You.
她们实际上停靠在很远的北部 大概是建造中的新码头附近
They are actually docked way far to the north where the new pier is being worked on.
同时 我们可能看不太清她们
And we may not get the cleanest view of them.
那么 我只需要给你看看只要读下说明书号的另外一个视角
So I'm just gonna give you another view of Just Read the Instructions.
所以 你能在我们离开前完全搞懂她
So you can soak that all in before we move on.
我们能在这里看到港口当局开始建造那些新码头
The view we have here is where the Port Authority has begun construction on the new docks
将会容许航天船队进一步发展
that will house space fleets going forward.
你可以看到航天器装配大楼就在后面 若隐若现
You can see the VAB lurking in the background there.
这就在6号货运码头的北端
This is at the north end of cargo pier 6.
而我们期待着能看到OCISLY号
And we are expecting to see Of Course I Still Love You
以及她旁边的只要读下说明书号
and Just Read the Instructions dock side by side
大约在那里你可以看到现在停靠的这些拖船
roughly where you can see these tugs docked right now.
吊车所在的位置 就是他们操作打桩机的地方
The crane is the current location of where they're working on the pilings.
但是你可以看到一点Finn Falgout号 的轮廓
But you can see a hint of Finn Falgout got back there.
那些灯正在向我发光 还有OCISLY号
Those are the lights that are actually shining toward me and Of Course I Still Love You
所以他们正准备去完成任务
so they are getting ready to leave for mission.
为了让你理解 这些和剩下的船队有什么关系
To give you an idea of what this looks like in relationship to where the rest of the fleet is
我们要去那儿仔细看看 你看到海岸警卫队就在那里
we're just gonna go over you see the Coast Guard right there
然后那里是GO Tree女士 GO Chief女士
and then we've got GO Ms. Tree, GO Ms. Chief
然后有点远的位置是只要读下说明书号
and a little bit farther over you've got Just Read the Instructions
而那个港口的吊机现在常用于吊起一级火箭
and that port crane that is often used now for the boosters.
而那个是6号货运码头 而这边是海岸警卫队
So that's cargo pier six and this is Coast Guard
而北部那边他们正在准备着OCISLY号
and the north and where they are readying Of Course I Still Love You.
那么现在港口里的事情比我们所孰知的要安静一些
So things are a little bit quieter in port than we're used to.
当然 这是由于佛罗里达州对社交距离的限制 以及对人们留在家里的要求
Of course this is due to the social distancing restrictions in the stay-at-home order that is in effect in Florida.
你可以看到我这位长着漂亮羽毛的朋友
You can see my fine-feathered friend here.
他是现在靠近我的唯一的朋友
He's the only friend near me right now
这就是为什么我现在没有戴口罩
which is why I'm not wearing my mask at the moment.
因为没人需要我保持社交距离
There is nobody to social distance from around me.
现在 确实有两个游轮停泊在港口
Right now we do actually have a couple of cruise ships that are docked.
雇佣驾驶员的成本实际上是很高的
It is actually quite expensive to hire the pilot services
这也是为什么它们经常停在这里
and sit at the dock which is why more often than not.
它们来了 加油 补给 然后它们回去了
They come in, they refuel, they resupply and then they do go back out.
并且留在卡纳维拉尔角海岸外边儿 在可可比奇和卡纳维拉尔角附近
And stay off the coast of Port Canaveral near Cocoa Beach and Cape Canaveral.
再给你看看我到底在哪儿
Give you just one more view here of where I am.
现在允许划船
Boating is allowed right now.
并且当你在水面上的时候 这其实是一个不错的保持社交距离的方法
And it is a pretty good way to social distance when you're out on the water.
现在的要求是 小船之间需要保持15.24米的距离
The current requirements do mean that boats do need to stay 50 feet away from each other
许多小码头都贴出这些标牌
and many of the marinas are putting up signs
说明社交距离至少需要1.83米
that are showing social distancing required remaining six feet apart
当你准备出发去一日游的时候
as you prepare to leave for your your day trip.
再偷偷看看只要读下说明书号
A sneak one more look here across at Just Read the Instructions,
看上去他们会在今天白天晚些时候进行工作
it does appear they are continuing to work on her even later in the day today.
所以 希望我们会在今年晚些时候看到她们参与任务
So hopefully we'll see them on mission later on this year.
我鼓励大家给我提问
I encourage you all to get any questions you have ready.
我会和Chris Gebhardt一道帮忙报导第7次星链任务
I will be helping cover the seventh StarLink mission with Chris Gebhardt
同时我们计划直播发射过程
and we plan to do a live stream of the launch.
以上就是今天我在卡角这段时间的总结
That concludes my time in Port Canaveral for today.
我会留意海上的交通
I'll be keeping an eye on marine traffic.
所以我们能知道第7次星链任务回收工作的确切开始时间
So that we know exactly when the seventh StarLink mission recovery operations begin.
我期待这件事会发生在周日晚上或者周一早上
I look for that to happen probably Sunday night or Monday morning.
之后 GO 寻求号就会出发 紧接着Finn Falgout号和OCISLY号
And then we'll have GO Quest leave-behind Finn Falgout and Of Course I Still Love You
而姐妹船GO Chief女士和GO Tree女士会在它们后面
and the sisters GO Ms. Chief and GO Ms. Tree should be behind them
因为这俩女士可以更快地前往回收区域
as they can get out to that recovery zone a little bit faster.
我期待着在发射日布置好我的相机
I look forward to putting out my cameras on launch day
和Chris Gebhardt一道 我们会给你们在油管上带来此次发射的直播
and Chris Gebhardt and I will be teaming up to bring you live coverage of the launch on YouTube.
所以一定要继续关注NASASpaceflight在Twitter上的更多的更新
So make sure you stay tuned to NASASpaceflight on Twitter for more updates on that.
我们会在幕后采纳一些有创意性的保持社交距离的方法
We will be doing some creative social distancing behind the camera.
这样我俩都可以参与直播
So that we can each participate in that one.
确保提出你们的问题
Make sure you bring your questions.
我们喜欢回答关于任务 船队
We love to answer questions about the mission, the fleet
或者即将在5月份发生的DM2任务
or of course upcoming DM2 which should be happening wow in May.
这真的让人兴奋
That's so super exciting.
这样我们可以告诉你们一些关于发射的信息
So we can give you some insight into what launch viewing may look like for that.
请持续关注NASASpaceflight
Until then stay tuned to NASASpaceflight.
保持社交距离 尽量呆在家里
Social distance and stay at home if you can.
祝你们安全
You all stay safe now.
再见
Goodbye.